A Guide to the Russell Sage Foundation records FA015
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Russell Sage Foundation records, 1974-2002; 2; 120 Cubic Feet 252 document boxes.
  - Grants, 1974-2002; 3; 52.5 Cubic Feet
    - Heckman, James, An Evaluation of Social Programs With a Special Focus on Government, 978.726, 1991-1995 (Box 109, Folder 843A)
    - Heckman, James, An Evaluation of Social Programs With a Special Focus on Government, 978.726, Attachment File I, 1993-1994 (Box 109, Folder 844)
    - Heckman, James, An Evaluation of Social Programs With a Special Focus on Government, 978.726, Attachment File II, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 845)
    - Heckman, James, The Impact of Tax and Subsidy Policies on Skill, 859.501, 1994-2000 (Box 110, Folder 846)
    - Heckman, James, The Impact of Tax and Subsidy Policies on Skill, 859.501, 1994-2000 (Box 110, Folder 846A)
    - Heckman, James, The Impact of Tax and Subsidy Policies on Skill, 859.501, Attachment File, 1998 (Box 110, Folder 847)
    - Heckman, James and Peter Siegelman, Presidential Grant Authority, The Design and Analysis of Audit Pair Sutdies to Assess Discrimination in Hiring, 99-93-03, 1992-2001 (Box 110, Folder 848)
    - Hedges, Larry, Does Money Matter? A Research Synthesis of the Relationship Between Educational Inputs and Student Outscomes, 899.301, 1993-1997 (Box 110, Folder 849)
    - Hedges, Larry, Does Money Matter? A Research Synthesis of the Relationship Between Educational Inputs and Student Outscomes, 899.301, Attachment File, 1981-1993 (Box 111, Folder 850)
    - Heinz, John P. and Edward O. Laumann, Study of the Chicago Bar Association, 1974-1979 (Box 111, Folder 851)
    - Heinz, John P. and Edward O. Laumann, Study of the Chicago Bar Association, 1974-1979 (Box 111, Folder 851A)
    - Heinz, John P. and Edward O. Laumann, Study of the Chicago Bar Association, Attachment File I, 1979 (Box 111, Folder 852)
    - Heinz, John P. and Edward O. Laumann, Study of the Chicago Bar Association, Attachment File I, 1979 (Box 111, Folder 852A)
    - Heinz, John P. and Edward O. Laumann, Study of the Chicago Bar Association, Attachment File II, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 853)
    - Heinz, John P. and Edward O. Laumann, Study of the Chicago Bar Association, Attachment File II, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 853A)
    - Herrnstein, Richard, A Series of Experiments on Principles Governing Choices that are Repeated Over Time, 998.920, 1989-1996 (Box 111, Folder 854)
    - Herrnstein, Richard, A Series of Experiments on Principles Governing Choices that are Repeated Over Time, 998.920, 1989-1996 (Box 111, Folder 854A)
    - Herrnstein, Richard, A Series of Experiments on Principles Governing Choices that are Repeated Over Time, 998.920, Attachment File, 1972-1992 (Box 111, Folder 855)
    - Herzenberg, Stephen, Enhancing Sercurity and Careers in Laboring and Clerical and Administrative Occupations, 85-97-01, 1996-1999 (Box 112, Folder 856)
    - Heydebrand, Wolf, Adjudication vs. Administration, An Organizational Analysis, 1974-1987 (Box 112, Folder 857)
    - Heymann, Jody, Work Hours, Night and Weekend Shifts and Changing Schedules: Their Effect on Health and Welfare of Families Living in Poverty and Single Parent Families, 999.402, 1993-1996 (Box 112, Folder 858)
    - Heymann, Jody, Work Hours, Night and Weekend Shifts and Changing Schedules: Their Effect on Health and Welfare of Families Living in Poverty and Single Parent Families, 999.402, 1993-1996 (Box 112, Folder 858A)
    - Hiatt, Howard, Broadening the Residency Training Program to Social Science, 979.506, 1994-2000 (Box 112, Folder 859)
    - Hill, Martha, Intergenerational Aspects of Economic Dependency, 99-89-32, 1989-1997 (Box 112, Folder 860)
    - Hill, Martha, Intergenerational Aspects of Economic Dependency, 99-89-32, 1989-1997 (Box 112, Folder 860A)
    - Hill, Martha, Intergenerational Aspects of Economic Dependency, 99-89-32, Attachment File, 1990 (Box 112, Folder 861)
    - Hogan, Dennis P. and Daniel T. Lichter, 1990 Census Project, The Living Arrangements and Welfare of Children and Youth, 908.108, 1991-1996 (Box 112, Folder 862)
    - Hogan, Dennis P. and Daniel T. Lichter, 1990 Census Project, The Living Arrangements and Welfare of Children and Youth, 908.108, 1991-1996 (Box 112, Folder 862A)
    - Hogarth, Robin and Howard Kunreuther, A Joint Study of Decision Making in Insurance Markets, 1989-1996 (Box 113, Folder 863)
    - Hogarth, Robin and Howard Kunreuther, A Joint Study of Decision Making in Insurance Markets, 1989-1996 (Box 113, Folder 863A)
    - Hogarth, Robin and Howard Kunreuther, A Joint Study of Decision Making in Insurance Markets, Attachment File, 1991-1993 (Box 113, Folder 864)
    - Holzer, Harry J., A Pilot Survey on Employer Hiring Procedures, 1991-1992 (Box 113, Folder 865)
    - Holzer, Harry J., Survey of Employer Hiring Procedures, 998.972, 1992-1996 (Box 113, Folder 866)
    - Holzer, Harry J., Survey of Employer Hiring Procedures, 998.972, Attachment File, 1993 (Box 113, Folder 867)
    - Hope, Keith, The Political Conception of Merit, 1977-1983 (Box 113, Folder 868)
    - Horton, Raymond D., Setting Municipal Priorities 1982, 1980-1982 (Box 113, Folder 869)
    - Hunt, Earl, Preporation of a Monograph on Intelligence and the World of Work. 978.721, 1990-1993 (Box 114, Folder 870)
    - Hunt, Earl, Preparation of a Monograph on Intelligence and the World of Work, 978.721, 1990-1993 (Box 114, Folder 870A)
    - Hunt, Morton, A Primer Research Synthesis, Who Shall Decide When Doctors Disagree, 899.402, 1994-1997 (Box 114, Folder 871)
    - Hunt, Morton, A Primer Research Synthesis, Who Shall Decide When Doctors Disagree, 899.402, 1994-1997 (Box 114, Folder 871A)
    - Hunt, Morton, A Primer Research Synthesis, Who Shall Decide When Doctors Disagree, 899.402, Attachment File, 1991-1994 (Box 114, Folder 872)
    - Hyman, Herbert, A Personal History of Survey Research, 1983-1990 (Box 114, Folder 873)
    - Hyman, Herbert, A Personal History of Survey Research, Attachment File I, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 874)
    - Hyman, Herbert, A Personal History of Survey Research, Attachment File II, 1985-1987 (Box 114, Folder 875)
    - Independent Sector (Formerly: The Coalition of National Voluntary Organizations), Gardner, John W. and Brian O'Connell, Research Activities and Conferences, 1980-1985 (Box 115, Folder 876)
    - Inkeles, Alex, Cross-National Research on the Growth of Due Process Litigation, 1981-1987 (Box 115, Folder 876)
    - Inkeles, Alex, Cross-National Research on the Growth of Due Process Litigation, Attachment File, 1980 (Box 115, Folder 878)
    - Iovenko, Michael, Joint Conference on Urban Youth Education, Training and Job Creation, 85-96-02, 1995-1997 (Box 115, Folder 879)
    - Iovenko, Michael, Joint Conference on Urban Youth Education, Training and Job Creation, 85-96-02, Attachment File, 1996 (Box 115, Folder 880)
    - Jacobs, Lawrence, Politicization of Public Opinion, 869.408, 1994-1997 (Box 115, Folder 881)
    - Jacobs, Lawrence, Politicization of Public Opinion, 869.408, 1994-1997 (Box 115, Folder 881A)
    - Jargowsky, Paul, Ghetto Poverty: The Neighborhood Distribution Framework, 998.974, 1992-1997 (Box 115, Folder 882)
    - Jargowsky, Paul, Ghetto Poverty: The Neighborhood Distribution Framework, 998.974, 1992-1997 (Box 115, Folder 882A)
      Restricted - Contains some time sensitive material --- open in 2018; and some permanently restricted material - confidential
    - Jargowsky, Paul, Ghetto Poverty: The Neighborhood Distribution Framework, 998.974, Attachment File, 1991-1993 (Box 116, Folder 883)
    - Jasanoff, Sheila, Scientific Information and Public Decision-Making on Cancer-Causing Substances: An International Comparaison, 1983-1986 (Box 116, Folder 884)
    - Jasanoff, Sheila, Scientific Information and Public Decision-Making on Cancer-Causing Substances: An International Comparaison, 1983-1986 (Box 116, Folder 884A)
    - Jencks, Christopher, Poverty and Hardship in America, 998.702, 1986-2000 (Box 116, Folder 885)
    - Jencks, Christopher, Poverty and Hardship in America, 998.702, 1986-2000 (Box 116, Folder 885A)
    - Jencks, Christopher, Poverty and Hardship in America, 998.702, Attachment File, 1986-1995 (Box 116, Folder 886)
    - Jencks, Christopher, Conference: Material Hardship in the United States and Europe, 1989-1996 (Box 116, Folder 887)
    - Jencks, Christopher, Meritocracy and Equality, 979.504, 1995-1998 (Box 116, Folder 888)
    - Jencks, Christopher, Conference on Meritocracy and Inequality, 1996 September 26-27, 1994, 1996 (Box 116, Folder 889)
    - Jenkins, J. Craig, Presidential Grant, The Politics of Social Reform: Recent Social Movements, Private Philanthropy and Democratic Institutions, 1982-1991 (Box 117, Folder 890)
    - Jenkins, J. Craig, Presidential Grant, The Politics of Social Reform: Recent Social Movements, Private Philanthropy and Democratic Institutions, Attachment File, 1983-1988 (Box 117, Folder 891)
    - Jenness, David, Preparation of a Guide to Federal Government Sources or Research Sources, 1981-1988 (Box 117, Folder 892)
    - Jenness, David, Preparation of a Guide to Federal Government Sources or Research Sources, Attachment File, 1981-1987 (Box 117, Folder 893)
    - Jessor, Richard, Conference on Ethnographic Approaches to the Study of Human Development, 959.301, 1991-1994 (Box 117, Folder 894)
    - Jewell, Malcolm E., Conference on Cooperative State Polling, 1980-1981 (Box 117, Folder 895)
    - Johnson, James, Jr., For Duties as Director of Multi-City Survey of Urban Inequality, 999.305, 1993-1996 (Box 117, Folder 896)
    - Juster, F. Thomas and John Laitner, A Study of Savings Behavior Based on TIAA/CREF Pension Holders, 988.923, 1990-1994 (Box 118, Folder 897)
    - Juster, F. Thomas and John Laitner, A Study of Savings Behavior Based on TIAA/CREF Pension Holders, 988.923, 1990-1994 (Box 118, Folder 897A)
    - Juster, F. Thomas and John Laitner, A Study of Savings Behavior Based on TIAA/CREF Pension Holders, 988.923, Attachement File, 1990-1993 (Box 118, Folder 898)
    - Kagan, Robert, Symposium on Law and Social Science, 97-96-04, 1995-1999 (Box 118, Folder 899)
    - Kagan, Robert, Symposium on Law and Social Science, 97-96-04, 1995-1999 (Box 118, Folder 899A)
    - Kagel, John, Judgmental Errors in Market Settings: The Winner's Curse in Construction Industry and OCS Building, 988.921, 1989-1994 (Box 118, Folder 900)
    - Kagel, John, Judgmental Errors in Market Settings: The Winner's Curse in Construction Industry and OCS Building, 988.921, 1989-1994 (Box 118, Folder 900A)
    - Kagel, John, Judgmental Errors in Market Settings: The Winner's Curse in Construction Industry and OCS Building, 988.921, Attachment File, 1992-1993 (Box 118, Folder 901)
    - Kahneman, Daniel, Summer Institute in Behavioral Economics, 989.401, 1993-1996 (Box 118, Folder 902)
    - Kahneman, Daniel, Summer Institute in Behavioral Economics, 989.401, Attachment File, 1994-1995 (Box 119, Folder 903)
    - Kahneman, Daniel, Ed Diener, and Norbert Schwarz, Elements of Quality of Life: Methods and Findings in the Study of Experienced Utility, 98-96-04, 1994-1999 (Box 119, Folder 904)
    - Kahneman, Daniel, Ed Diener, and Norbert Schwarz, Elements of Quality of Life: Methods and Findings in the Study of Experienced Utility, 98-96-04, 1994-1999 (Box 119, Folder 904A)
    - Kalleberg, Anne L. and Robert P. Althauser, The Effects of Labor Markets on Careers, 1978-1982 (Box 119, Folder 905)
    - Kalleberg, Anne L. and Robert P. Althauser, The Effects of Labor Markets on Careers, 1978-1982 (Box 119, Folder 905A)
    - Kane, Thomas, Sending the Kids to College, 859.508, 1995-2000 (Box 119, Folder 906)
    - Kane, Thomas, Sending the Kids to College, 859.508, 1995-2000 (Box 119, Folder 906A)
    - Kanter, Rosabeth Moss, Study Entitled: Corporate Progressivism: How and Why Institutions Respond to Changing Societal Roles and Expectations, 1983-1985 (Box 120, Folder 907)
    - Kanter, Rosabeth Moss, Study Entitled: Corporate Progressivism: How and Why Institutions Respond to Changing Societal Roles and Expectations, 1983-1985 (Box 120, Folder 907A)
    - Kasanda, John, 1990 Census Project, Changes in Industrial Structure and Implications of the Changing Location of Employment, 90-81-10, 1991-1997 (Box 120, Folder 908)
    - Kasanda, John, 1990 Census Project, Changes in Industrial Structure and Implications of the Changing Location of Employment, 90-81-10, 1991-1997 (Box 120, Folder 908A)
    - Kasinitz, Philip, Study Entitles: Red Hook: Urban Space and the Origins of the Underclass, 99-89-55, 1991-2001 (Box 120, Folder 909)
    - Kasperson, Roger E. and Robert W. Kates, Hazard Management in Industry, 1981-1988 (Box 120, Folder 910)
    - Kasperson, Roger E. and Robert W. Kates, Hazard Management in Industry, 1981-1988 (Box 120, Folder 910A)
    - Kasperson, Roger E. and Robert W. Kates, Hazard Management in Industry, Attachment File, 1981 (Box 120, Folder 911)
    - Kaufman, Robert, Presidential Grant, Organizational Variation and National Selection: A Theory of Organizational Evolution, 1982-1984 (Box 120, Folder 912)
    - Kirp, David L. and Mark G. Yudof, Gender Justice, 1981 (Box 120, Folder 913)
    - Kirp, David L. and Mark G. Yudof, Gender Justice, 1981 (Box 120, Folder 913A)
    - Kirp, David L. and Mark G. Yudof, Gender Justice, Attachment File, 1979-1984 (Box 120, Folder 914)
    - Kirp, David L. and Mark G. Yudof, Gender Justice, Attachment File, 1979-1984 (Box 121, Folder 914A)
    - Kirschenman, Joleen, Racial Stereotypes in the Workplace, 1991-1992 (Box 121, Folder 915)
    - Kleinman, Arthur, Ethics, Medicine and Social Science, 97-99-01, 1998-2002 (Box 121, Folder 916)
    - Kleinman, Arthur, Ethics, Medicine and Social Science, 97-99-01, 1998-2002 (Box 121, Folder 916A)
      Restricted - Contains some time sensitive material --- open in 2024; and some permanently restricted material - confidential
    - Kleinman, Arthur, Ethics, Medicine and Social Science, 97-99-01, Attachment File I, 1999 (Box 121, Folder 917)
    - Kleinman, Arthur, Ethics, Medicine and Social Science, 97-99-01, Attachment File II, 1999 (Box 121, Folder 918)
    - Klitgaard, Robert E., Presidential Grant, Public Policy in Developing Countries, 1984-1987 (Box 122, Folder 919)
    - Knoke, David, Presidential Grant, Research on Gender-Politics Organizations, 1985-1987 (Box 122, Folder 920)
    - Kornblum, William and Frank Bonilla, Research on Poverty and Education in the Bronx, 998.922, 1987-1996 (Box 122, Folder 921)
    - Kornblum, William and Frank Bonilla, Research on Poverty and Education in the Bronx, 998.922, Attachment File, 1987-1994 (Box 122, Folder 922)
    - Kraut, Alan G., National Conference on Research Synthesis, 899.401, 1993-1996 (Box 122, Folder 923)
    - Kraut, Alan G., National Conference on Research Synthesis, 899.401 Attachment File, 1994 (Box 122, Folder 924)
    - Kraut, Alan G., Summit Meeting of Scientific Psychological Societies, 97-97-15, 1997-1999 (Box 123, Folder 925)
    - Krieger, Martin H., Presidential Grant, Marginalism and Discontinuity in Decisionmaking and in Scientific Models, 1982-1990 (Box 123, Folder 926)
    - Krieger, Susan, Presidential Grant, Fiction and Social Science, 1984-1987 (Box 123, Folder 927)
    - Krieger, Susan, Presidential Grant, Fiction and Social Science, Attachment File, 1985 (Box 123, Folder 928)
    - Kryson, Maria, Racial Residential Preferences, 99-96-03, 1996-1999 (Box 123, Folder 929)
    - Kryson, Maria, Racial Residential Preferences, 99-96-03, 1996-1999 (Box 123, Folder 929A)
    - Lamont, Michele, Conference on Race, Class and Culture, VS-001, 501.232, 1996-1999 (Box 123, Folder 930)
    - Lamont, Michele, Conference on Race, Class and Culture, VS-001, 501.232, 1996-1999 (Box 123, Folder 930A)
    - Lamphere, Louise and Peter Evans, Working Families and Sunbelt Industrialization: Changes in the Home and Workplace, 1984-1993 (Box 123, Folder 931)
    - Lamphere, Louise and Peter Evans, Working Families and Sunbelt Industrialization: Changes in the Home and Workplace, 1984-1993 (Box 123, Folder 931A)
    - Lamphere, Louise and Peter Evans, Working Families and Sunbelt Industrialization: Changes in the Home and Workplace, Attachment File I, 1988 (Box 124, Folder 932)
    - Lamphere, Louise and Peter Evans, Working Families and Sunbelt Industrialization: Changes in the Home and Workplace, Attachment File II, 1985 (Box 124, Folder 933)
    - Lennon, Mary Clare, Low Quality Jobs and Trajectories of Unemployment: Consequences for the Psychological Well-Being of Adults and Children, 85-96-06, 1995-2000 (Box 124, Folder 934)
    - Lennon, Mary Clare, Low Quality Jobs and Trajectories of Unemployment: Consequences for the Psychological Well-Being of Adults and Children, 85-96-06, 1995-2000 (Box 124, Folder 934A)
    - Lerman, Robert I., Lee Rainwater, and Martin Rein, A Comparative Study of the Low Wage Jobs in Social Science Industries, 998.943, 998.713, 1988-1999 (Box 124, Folder 935)
    - Lerman, Robert I., Lee Rainwater, and Martin Rein, A Comparative Study of the Low Wage Jobs in Social Science Industries, 998.943, 998.713, 1988-1999 (Box 124, Folder 935A)
    - Lerman, Robert I., Lee Rainwater, and Martin Rein, A Comparative Study of the Low Wage Jobs in Social Science Industries, 998.943, 998.713, Attachment File, 1990-1994 (Box 124, Folder 936)
    - Levi, Margaret, Construction and Maintenance of Trust, 97-94-07, 1994-2000 (Box 125, Folder 937)
    - Levi, Margaret, Construction and Maintenance of Trust, 97-94-07, 1994-2000 (Box 125, Folder 937A)
    - Levi, Margaret, Construction and Maintenance of Trust, 97-94-07, Attachment File I, 1994 (Box 125, Folder 938)
    - Levi, Margaret, Construction and Maintenance of Trust, 97-94-07, Attachment File II, 1990-1994 (Box 125, Folder 939)
    - Levi, Margaret, The Impact of Economics on Politcal Science: A Conversation with Nobel Laureates, 97-97-08, 1996-2000 (Box 125, Folder 940)
    - Levi, Margaret, The Impact of Economics on Politcal Science: A Conversation with Nobel Laureates, 97-97-08, Attachment File I, 1997 (Box 125, Folder 941)
    - Levi, Margaret, The Impact of Economics on Politcal Science: A Conversation with Nobel Laureates, 97-97-08, Attachment File II, 1997-1998 (Box 126, Folder 942)
    - Levine, David and Gary Charness, Preceptions of the Fair Employment Contract: A Quasi-Experiment, 98-99-01, 1998-1999 (Box 126, Folder 943)
    - Levine, Felice, Millennial Milestone: A Switching Crisis in Sociology, 97-97-04, 1997-1999 (Box 126, Folder 944)
    - Levine, Felice, Millennial Milestone: A Switching Crisis in Sociology, 97-97-04, 1997-1999 (Box 126, Folder 944A)
    - Levine, Felice, Millennial Milestone: A Switching Crisis in Sociology, 97-97-04, Attachment File I, 1998 (Box 126, Folder 945)
    - Levine, Felice, Millennial Milestone: A Switching Crisis in Sociology, 97-97-04, Attachment File II, 1997 (Box 127, Folder 946)
    - Levinsohn, James, Productivity, Jobs and International Competition, 85-97-20, 1997-2000 (Box 127, Folder 947)
    - Levinsohn, James, Productivity, Jobs and International Competition, 85-97-20, 1997-2000 (Box 127, Folder 947A)
    - Levy, Frank, Living Standards and Distribution of Income 1960-1980, 1982-1987 (Box 127, Folder 948)
    - Levy, Frank, Distribution of Individuals' and Families' Lifetime Incomes, 998.715, 1988-1996 (Box 127, Folder 949)
    - Levy, Frank, Presidential Authority Grant, Testing the "Mismatch Hypothesis": Birth Patterns, Education and the Occupational Structure, 998.924, 1989-1996 (Box 127, Folder 950)
    - Levy, Frank, Presidential Authority Grant, Testing the "Mismatch Hypothesis": Birth Patterns, Education and the Occupational Structure, 998.924, 1989-1996 (Box 127, Folder 950A)
    - Levy, Frank, 1990 Census Project, "Changes in Distribution of Income and Trends in Poverty", 909.304, 1992-1996 (Box 127, Folder 951)
    - Levy, Frank, 1990 Census Project, "Changes in Distribution of Income and Trends in Poverty", 909.304, Attachment File, 1991-1992 (Box 127, Folder 952)
    - Levy, Frank, 'Dollars and Dreams' Updated, 90-96-01, 1995-1999 (Box 127, Folder 953)
    - Levy, Frank, 'Dollars and Dreams' Updated, 90-96-01, 1995-1999 (Box 127, Folder 953A)
    - Liebman, Jeffery, Reforming Tax and Transfer Programs in Order to Assist Low-Skilled Workers, 85-97-12, 1997-2000 (Box 127, Folder 954)
    - Liebman, Jeffery, Reforming Tax and Transfer Programs in Order to Assist Low-Skilled Workers, 85-97-12, 1997-2000 (Box 128, Folder 954A)
    - Liebman, Jeffery, Reforming Tax and Transfer Programs in Order to Assist Low-Skilled Workers, 85-97-12, Attachment File, 2000 (Box 128, Folder 955)
    - Lin, Ann Chih, Politics of Crime Policy, 869.501, 1994-1998 (Box 128, Folder 956)
    - Lindenberg, Siegwart, Edit Proceedings of the Thomas-Znaniecki Conference on Contemporary Social Theory, 1983-1984 (Box 128, Folder 957)
    - Lindblom, Charles E., Probing a Society's Problems, 1984-1990 (Box 128, Folder 958)
    - Lindblom, Charles E., Probing a Society's Problems, 1984-1990 (Box 128, Folder 958A)
    - Lipset, Seymour M. and Earl Raab, Presidential Grant, A Research Assistance Award for a Project on the Jewish Experience in the United States, 978.710, 1988-1995 (Box 128, Folder 959)
    - Lipsey, Mark W., Meta-analysis of Juvenile Delinquency Treatment Effectiveness Research, 1988-1992 (Box 128, Folder 960)
    - Lipsey, Mark W., Meta-analysis of Juvenile Delinquency Treatment Effectiveness Research, 1988-1992 (Box 128, Folder 960A)
    - Lipsey, Mark W., Meta-analysis of Juvenile Delinquency Treatment Effectiveness Research, Attachment File, 1990-1991 (Box 128, Folder 961)
    - Lipsky, Michael, Politics of Street-Level Bureaucracy, 1972-1978 (Box 128, Envelope 962)
    - Locke, Herbert G., Dael Wolfe Endowment for Excellence in Public Affairs, 1986 (Box 129, Folder 963)
    - Loewenstein, George, Working Group on Intertemporal Choice, 98-89-28 & 98-87-05, 1987-2003 (Box 129, Folder 964)
    - Loewenstein, George, Working Group on Intertemporal Choice, 98-89-28 & 98-87-05, Attachment File, 1989-2001 (Box 129, Folder 965)
    - Loewenstein, George, Working Group on Intertemporal Choice, 98-89-28 & 98-87-05, Attachment File, 1989-2001 (Box 129, Folder 965A)
    - Loewenstein, George, Neurobehavioral Economics, 98-97-01, 1995-1998 (Box 129, Folder 966)
    - Loh, Wallace D. and Neil Vidmar, Source Book on Law and Psychology, 1975-1986 (Box 129, Folder 967)
    - Lorber, Judith, Gender and Society, 1986-1994 (Box 129, Folder 968)
    - Lynn, Laurence E., Jr., Presidential Grant, Public Policies, Private Choices and Economic Hardship, 98-89-03, 1989-1996 (Box 129, Folder 969)
    - MaCurdy, Thomas and Anne Royalty, Contribution of Non-Wage Benefits to the Growth and Inequality of Labor Compensation, 85-97-15, 1997-2001 (Box 130, Folder 970)
    - MaCurdy, Thomas and Anne Royalty, Contribution of Non-Wage Benefits to the Growth and Inequality of Labor Compensation, 85-97-15, 1997-2001 (Box 130, Folder 970A)
    - MaCurdy, Thomas and Anne Royalty, Contribution of Non-Wage Benefits to the Growth and Inequality of Labor Compensation, 85-97-15, Attachment File, 2000-2001 (Box 130, Folder 971)
    - Maital, Sharone and Shlomo Maital, A Book Project Entitled: The Myopic Society, 98-89-31, 1991-1998 (Box 130, Folder 972)
    - Maital, Sharone and Shlomo Maital, A Book Project Entitled: The Myopic Society, 98-89-31, 1991-1998 (Box 130, Folder 972A)
    - Maital, Sharone and Shlomo Maital, A Book Project Entitled: The Myopic Society, 98-89-31, Attachment File I, 1993 (Box 130, Folder 973)
    - Maital, Sharone and Shlomo Maital, A Book Project Entitled: The Myopic Society, 98-89-31, Attachment File II, 1992-1994 (Box 131, Folder 974)
    - Mare, Robert D., 1990 Census Project, Changes in Educational Attainment, School Enrollment and Skills Levels, 90-81-05, 1991-1996 (Box 131, Folder 975)